Jhal
a very good morning friends welcome you all
request show a drive safe mission possible as it is
possible permissions possible to make roads safer
and also refer to everyone who is
using this role welcome you all question to
subscribe yaar representing give five to
tough questions in hum budhe khajoor and seventh
day and the volume to be coming with the
question and participate and win
exciting prizes with now with knowledge about you
ready for the first question of
this hair oil screen is
200 abs and I screen you are
lt or else kasana a welcome you to
point question should arrive safe for mission
possible for married for you
that union you tika left on adat
intersections venture highway you notice any vehicle already in
the highway approach in this
point you well otherwise chal chup pas vikat was already
on highway and you  To any way will harm to
show you want forest and
drove fast don't post sapna athey
request you to please come and join this can be
drawn in be a part of this and now
you can use them then win exciting prizes for
the question you have only to today and you can
register your answer on appropriate is possible you like you can
also win a prize request
you to kindly join this campaign with your
family of range your love ones they can also be
part of this and you can also be like this
rules and nadi ke not show up in his skill
about and road safety sudhar salute in
lord vishnu camp in about how to make
roads and how to change driving behavior
like on a daily basis and don't know what to do but still something which
but judge ne nahi first
tip is that in India is very very before this how doobi
change karo mein bhi logon ne
bahut zyada apne behavior change isko
change kar hai aur hum log jo  We could not wait for 2 minutes
if we had gone to our
mother's place to buy something or for shopping, so now it was we who would get so many
impressions, first
me first me, but you during this time
we had started following social distancing,
we used to let the people who were ahead of us go and
come, only
after that we used to go and do our work comfortably,
so somewhere we have brought about that behaviour change, we have
proved that this
sweet can change and we can change, Indian
roads will, so these are such that if
someone is deleting you or doing something, then
you can write, if you have some patience then you will be able to
stay safe yourself and will also let that other
person stay safe, if someone is in a
hurry then okay, then you let him go, there is no
problem, then
you can see the ice cream,
we will need to check, all the best,
today at the intersection to enter the highway, you will
notice already nearby Indore highway
approaching spot, you have to take a left turn
from the intersection  Enters
towards the highway, you have to take the laptop
and you see that the equal vehicle has already bent and the one
which is on the highway is about to come at the
same spot from where you have to take the toll,
what will you do at that time, there is an
option of alarm, stop the vehicle and the vehicle is already
developed and the highway is on, now the one which is going to come
there, you will let him go
because he is already on the highway or
you can tow anywhere, you have seen it,
okay he is driving there but still you will toll,
you will already be standing there,
you will tell him by blowing the horn
that you will turn on, no, dam, last
virus, drive fast, train faster, now quickly and
increase your speed and
try to toll quickly, so please come
join us and
see the answer to this question and half an hour this and the lesson of this champion,
Bankhedi, you can also gift something, you
can also become a responsible citizen,
America Ring Road Safety Awareness, so
tell us which one will you choose
from these and you must have seen this, then you will see it
on Delhi 20  You will get to see
this kind of situation
on the road every day and we have seen the run-up that this oh Komal
[Music] yes,
this is what happened at your office,
so this Shubh Librarian returned to
Nutrikunna Road fixed, anytime anyone
from anywhere comes on our daily, be it
animals, be it the difference, be
it the intersection, people who are doing wuzu ilaj,
cars also sometimes add here, so
we drink their juice,
all that is a lot, so this also returned and
now time som woh is much, answer
and tell us your experience, how much
knowledge you have about it and Amazing
is leaning towards eunuchs, this is our cement today,
and Modi ji, we come on 20, it has been 07
days since we have reached zero, everyday
we come with 5 questions,
every 22 hours we have
thank you, they come and share their questions
with everyone, you interesting
Parts that you can register your answer in those five attempts,
you have the patience to
buy not one but multiple gifts, which are
its pimples,
our show comes now speaking in that,
we publish our results
on daily basis and you can add to it in the end, you can
see your results, it
comes on our SIM channel, you can go there and give your
answer, the link is given below,
now go and click on the diary there and give
your answer, we go
because Om you should bring your family and friends
along too because the people you
love, their Avengers are also
those,
Om Avenish should be increased
regarding road safety because those people
also use it every day, whether it is
big or small,
everyone has to use it, so our
aim of this entire campaign, of all these
things is that how can we
make our daily life just
and how can we take action  We can make people as
illegal as possible so that we
can work
on the accidents because if everyone
follows their responsibilities and follows their rules, if
you use process gas, then
somewhere or the other, more major accidents happen in
which we lose people,
we should be able to prevent those things somewhere, if something happens due to
a technical fault, that is
an accident, but if due to our mistake
we make ourselves even more
android, that is foolishness and carelessness,
we should not be careless, but
like a responsible citizen, we should
use the rose with our responsibilities, we have been widely
spread, you know
what are your rules and regulations,
you should follow them, if you are
running a chicken treatment, then what things should you take
care of, and if you are
running a light or a mill, then
what things should you take care of,
all those things should be taken care of from the point of
view of our safety, so that we do
not suffer much loss, and especially those who are in the
villages, we have seen the
most  Happy patients are those people
and those who have a two-wheeler have a good
impression
and Lord, they do not
understand that their conduct
with the road is 90% bad, that is, evening with saint,
daily pair link direct conduct,
if anything happens to you then their
conduct by drowning is very high,
daily but Dixit is also there, that growth is not
good, you all should be good, but two-
wheeler people should be very patient
because we have seen that on our elastic
delete, you see that two-wheelers are
black, their bus does not present at all,
if you
try to walk by making even a little difference in the corners, then they
cross even from that,
we can dream that
wearing a helmet is a point for them because
after falling you can directly get a head injury due to
which there can be a media entry, even then
every
time I am requesting you to please do
not go out of the house without your helmet,
you should always wear a helmet, keep your life
safe, the helmet is a weapon
and a  It creates a covering It's always
important to buy helmets It
creates a covering Thank you
and protects your body
We can save your life from any major injury
If you try to keep yourself safe
Now wear a helmet And the helmet that you wear is also
requesting you to please keep it
tight If you don't wear it like that If you wear it like that It could happen during the accident It could go out
of your mind and you could get injured So they
request you to please use your helmet Sixteen
years have them
that their husbands use them and
keep themselves safe Only then will we be successful in this entire campaign
When we will be able to shave every person
daily
If we all fulfill our responsibilities together Then we will be able to
save our lives As you
can see on my screen The emotion Come back
to the question Last participant
in this You need to tackle fan habit intersection
which  Enter and highway viewers are already and
half improving spot you have to take left and
injection on to enter highway you have to
enter highway and you see that another one
he exit and release is on highway he is about to
come to the same spot so what will you do at that
time back your options are Allah
the royal chup pass pick up sid was already on
the highway no
you will let him go he will let him
exit because he is already on the highway
he will check himself and so you to anywhere you will
spot it because you were there so to show you don't
post you will
save the phone tell them that you will first ton
this drive fast train force and or
you will tone faster and name will
drive faster tone fast helpful
first don't do that so we saw this
question on Delhi Police you
see these things so come
join us register your answers
and be a part of this entire campaign
drive safe mission possible unit 10 we have to make this
mix possible drive
just make road safety a priority  New step,
new hope
is ours and ours, we have to
protect our people everyday, as you have seen, we have to
make useless force and define people for producers who use on the road
and how can we make that,
only with our and your cooperation we
can make our everyday, so you register your tears
and also on the bike with another set of questions after two
years, so you have
2 hours, please yourself and you
answer it quickly, we were listening to you
otherwise Kasana, thank you so much for the very
good morning and Om Shun Hindi tune,
thank you so much for